teelaunch.com 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policy | teelaunch

**Last modified: May 20, 2018**

imINDY LLC (“ **Company** ” or ** ** “ **We** ”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website www.teelaunch.com (our “ **Website** ”) or install our Teelaunch application on the Shopify platform (the “ **Application** ” as that term is defined in our End User License Agreement, which is incorporated herein by reference) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website and Application.
  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website or Application.
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
  * Information that third parties who use our Website or Application may collect from you and send to us after you place an order with them.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party except as stated above; or
  * any third party except as stated above, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, you should not use our Website or Application. By accessing or using this Website and the Application, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website or the Application after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Website and Application are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features or register on the Website, download the Application, make any purchases through the Website or Application, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [legal@teelaunch.com](mailto:legal@teelaunch.com).

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website and Application, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card information, or any other information the Website collects that is defined as personal or personally identifiable information under an applicable law (“ **Personal Information** ”); and
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.

Information You Provide to Us.  The information we collect on or through our Website and Application may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website or Application. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, uploading content, posting content, or installing our Application. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website or Application.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website or Application and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website or Application.
  * Your search queries on the Website or Application.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “ **Posted** ”) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or Application or third parties (collectively, “ **User Contributions** ” as that term is defined in our Terms of Use). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website or Application with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.  As you navigate through and interact with our Website or Application, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website or Application, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include Personal Information, but we may maintain it or associate it with Personal Information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and Application and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website or Application according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website or Application.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).**  A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * **Flash Cookies.**  Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.
  * **Web Beacons.**  Pages of the Website may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

We do not collect Personal Information automatically, but we may tie this information to Personal Information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

**Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.**

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website or Application are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your Personal Information or they may collect information, including Personal Information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Information:

  * To present our Website and Application and their contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website, Application, or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your Personal Information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose Personal Information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties (“Subprocessors”) we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep Personal Information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. Our Subprocessors are listed [here](https://teelaunch.com/pages/subprocessors).
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Company’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information held by the Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have consented to these disclosures.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an email address to use the “email a friend” feature of our Website, we will transmit the contents of that email and your email address to the recipients.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your Personal Information:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including responding to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](https://teelaunch.com/pages/terms), End User License Agreement (both Terms of Use and End User License Agreement are incorporated herein by reference), and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the Personal Information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.**  You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s [website](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * **Promotional Offers from the Company.**  If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out when you receive our emails or at any other time by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an email stating your request to [customerservice@teelaunch.com](mailto:customerservice@teelaunch.com). If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions.
  * Depending on your location, you may have certain rights with respect to your information, such as: (i) data access and portability (including the right to obtain a copy of your personal data you provided to the Company, through your account or by contacting us at [legal@teelaunch.com](mailto:legal@teelaunch.com) ; (ii) data correction (including the ability to update your personal data, through your account or by contacting us at [legal@teelaunch.com](mailto:legal@teelaunch.com)  ); (iii) data deletion (including the right to have the Company delete your personal information, except information we are required to retain, by contacting us at [legal@teelaunch.com](mailto:legal@teelaunch.com) ), or we may delete your data if we are instructed to do so by our customers who export your personal information to us, except for information we are required to retain; and (iv) withdrawal of consent or objection to processing (including, in limited circumstances, the right to ask the Company to stop processing your personal data, by contacting us at [legal@teelaunch.com](mailto:legal@teelaunch.com) ). If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our [Terms of Use](https://teelaunch.com/pages/terms).

We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“ **NAI** ”) on the NAI’s website.

**Data Security**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is behind a private IP and stored behind firewalls. All sensitive data will be encrypted using SSL technology, namely a 2048-bit SSL security certificate.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of Personal Information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ Personal Information, we will notify you by email. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

**Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:
